soulpancake.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Participant

**Effective Date:**  This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 14, 2017.

Welcome!  You have arrived at a website that is provided by Participant Media, LLC (“ **Company** ” or “ **we** ,” “ **our** ” or “ **us** ”).  This “ **Privacy Policy** ” governs your use of [www.participantmedia.com](http://www.participantmedia.com/), [www.participant.com](http://www.participant.com/), [www.soulpancake.com](http://www.soulpancake.com/), and also applies to your use of all features, applications, content, downloads, websites and other online services that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, referred to herein as the “ **Services** ”), regardless of how you access or use the Services, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to our data collection activities offline or otherwise outside of our Services (unless otherwise stated below).

The privacy of each and every user matters to us, and we strive for transparency in all of our data privacy practices, especially when it comes to identifying the information we collect, use, share, and disclose, as well as the ways we help keep your information safe.  Unless we have obtained your permission or otherwise disclosed it in this Privacy Policy, Company does not sell your personal information for our own financial gain, nor will we share your personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes without first offering you an opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of such sharing.  We take our responsibility to protect your information very seriously.  Please remember, we are always here to answer any questions you have, and we look forward to serving you for years to come.  **To the extent we provide you notice on our Services of different or additional privacy policies or practices ( _e.g._ , at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use.**

In addition, please review the Service’s [**Terms of Service**](http://www.participantmedia.com/terms-use), which governs your use of the Services.  _By using our Services_ , _you consent to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service and our collection, use and sharing of your information and data, and other activities, as described below._

_**Collection of Information**_

Company collects information from users in two ways.

First, we may collect names, email addresses, home addresses, telephone numbers, and any other information that may be used to identify you personally as an individual.  This type of data is often referred to as PII (personally identifiable information), and is most commonly collected when you submit information to us through a form on the Services.  We only collect PII from you when you use certain Services.  For example, if you sign up for a newsletter, participate in our brand ambassador program, or submit a customer service form, we may collect your name, address, telephone number, email, or other PII.

The other type of information we collect is more generic in nature and tells us about your online habits and preferences, like when you browse our Services.  These collection processes can also be used to help us offer a more entertaining and engaging experience.  This type of information doesn’t tell us who you are exactly, but it can tell us things like the pages you’ve viewed, how long you spend on our Services, what links you’ve clicked on, the time in which you view content, and where you are located.  This type of information is sometimes referred to as non-PII (non-personally identifiable information).  The type of non-PII we may collect from you includes information about what you look at on our Services, when you visit our Services, what advertisements you respond to, the types of devices you use (computer, tablet, smartphone, etc.), your IP address, links you follow from other websites, and content you engage with.  This type of information is sometimes combined to form aggregate data, which helps us summarize and analyze our customers’ experiences.  We also allow this type of information to be collected by ad networks.  An ad network is a company that connects advertisers to websites for the purpose of hosting advertisements.  We also employ the use of analytics providers, such as Google Analytics, that may gather this same type of information.  Aggregate data like this will not identify you individually and cannot be used to pinpoint any one specific person.

_**Use of Information**_

We may use your information for various purposes, including:

  * to provide you with information such as to send you electronic newsletters or to provide you with special offers or promotional and marketing materials on behalf of us or third parties, including to let you know about upcoming events;
  * to enable you to participate in a variety of the Services’ features such as to enable you to participate in online surveys, loyalty programs, entry sweepstakes, contests or other promotions;
  * to improve the Services, marketing endeavors or our Services offerings;
  * to customize your experience on the Services or to serve you specific content that we believe is relevant to you;
  * to provide customer support;
  * to contact you with regard to your use of the Services and, in our discretion, changes to the Services and/or Services’ policies;
  * to improve the overall experience at the Services;
  * for internal business purposes; and
  * for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

_**Sharing of Information**_

The PII we collect through your use of our Services may be shared with vendors who we may work with for reasons such as to provide these Services to you or to maintain our Services.

The non-PII information we gather about your interests and habits may also be shared as aggregate data (summarized information) or used by vendors for transactional or fulfillment purposes, such as to continue offering you relevant online services and improving our offerings.

_**Disclosure of Information**_

There may be times when we access or release your personal or general data to protect the legal rights or property of Company and its affiliates.  We might also use this information to protect the safety, security, and privacy of our users or members of the general public, especially in urgent situations.  Furthermore, we will use this information to protect against fraud and to comply with all U.S. laws and legal processes and rulings.

In addition, it is possible that we may transfer your information to another organization should we sell all or part of our business (or sell or transfer all or part of our assets).  During this process, your information would only be transferred to the party or parties involved in this transaction.

_**Social Networks and Sharing Features**_

Our Service offers social sharing features and other integrated tools.  These tools are created by other sites like Facebook (such as the Facebook Share button).  When you use these features or share any general or personal information through the use of these sites, you are bound by the privacy policies of these other services.  For example, if your post content from our website through a link on Facebook, you are then bound to Facebook’s privacy policies and terms of service.  These third parties may retain any information used or provided in any such communications or other activities and these third parties’ practices are not subject to our Privacy Policy.  Company may not control or have access to your communications through these third parties.  You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such third-party tools on our Services.

_**Cookies and Beacons**_

When you visit or interact with our Services, we may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to store certain pieces of information about your visit and interactions with our Service.  Your browser may allow you to remove or disable these cookies or web beacons.  However, if you do so, your experience on our Service will be affected, which means you may not be able to take advantage of certain features.  Further, third parties may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies in connection with our Service, which may include the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites and other online services.  We may also allow certain third parties, such as vendors, service providers and advertisers, to use the aggregate data obtained from cookies and web beacons.  Third-party use of this data is governed by their individual privacy policies.

_**Analytics Service Providers**_

We allow analytics companies to collect information about our users' computers or mobile devices and their online activities.  They do this using certain technologies that analyze this information.  We allow this to better deliver and improve our Services.  Analytics companies may use mobile device IDs, as described in the paragraph below (Mobile device IDs).  Unlike cookies, Mobile device IDs cannot be deleted.

We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as a DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our Services.  To learn more about how to opt out of Google’s use of the Google Analytics cookie, visit the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on  at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.  To learn more about how to opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies, visit the DoubleClick opt-out page at <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=e>.

If you want to learn more about the analytics services that we utilize, please contact us via our [Contact Us](http://www.participantmedia.com/contact) page and select “Privacy” from the Topic pulldown menu.

_**Ad Networks and Advertisements**_

We allow ad networks to advertise on our Services.  We may provide these ad networks with information about your interests and engagement with advertisements in order to help them customize ads on our Services and other sites you may visit.  This means that advertisements may be better suited to your specific interests and tailored to your preferences.  These networks track your online activities over time and across third party websites by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of the tracking technologies described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, and they use this information to show you advertisements (including our ads) that are tailored to your individual interests.  We do not provide any information that personally identifies you as an individual to any ad networks or advertisers.

We may use third-party advertising companies to target advertisements to you on our Services, across the web, on your mobile device and on any of your other devices, based on the information we have collected from and about you, as well as information relating to your and other users’ visits to this and other websites and online services.  To do so, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through the use of pixel tags) or recognize an identifier associated with your mobile device.  These companies may also use these technologies, along with PII they or we collect on the different devices you use, to recognize you across the devices you use, such as a mobile device and a laptop or other computer. 

To obtain a list of the ad network companies we work with and request their privacy policy information, please contact us via our [Contact Us](http://www.participantmedia.com/contact) page.  Further, you may visit [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to learn more about this type of advertising and how to opt-out of this form of advertising by companies participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) self-regulatory program.  Note that electing to opt-out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications, although it may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests.  In addition, note that if you use a different browser or erase cookies from your browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

_**Links**_

The Service may contain links to other websites or web pages not operated by us.  Company may also display advertisements from third-party companies not associated with Company.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites and advertising companies, nor are we responsible for the privacy policies of other web pages and services operated by organizations and persons outside of Company (even when we provide links on our Service and include them within our content).  Once you leave the Service via such a link, access a third-party application (such as widgets), or click on an advertisement, you are then governed by these outside privacy policies.  This means that you must follow and accept their terms of service and individual privacy policies.

_**Managing, Updating or Canceling Your Account**_

We may provide the ability for users to create and maintain personal accounts in connection with the Services.  In such event, you may change or update your personal data and account information by signing in and accessing Account Settings within your user profile.  You may also close your account on the Account Settings page.  If you wish to cancel or modify the email marketing communications you receive from us, you may do so by following the instructions contained within our promotional e-mails or by using the [Contact Us](http://www.participantmedia.com/contact) page.

**_Our Services are For a General Audience_**

Our Services are not directed towards individuals under the age of 13 and are not meant to be used or accessed by individuals under the age of 13.  We do not knowingly collect personal information, including phone numbers, addresses, and names, from users under the age of 13, and we will readily delete such information should this occur.  If you believe we might have any information from or about an individual under the age of 13, please contact us via our [Contact Us](http://www.participantmedia.com/contact) page.

_**California Privacy Rights**_

If you are a minor and also a registered and current user of our Service, you have the right under California law to request that we remove any information that may identify you personally.  You may also request that we make this information appear anonymous so that it cannot be traced back to you.  We will comply with these requests unless we are required to maintain your information under applicable state and federal laws.  If you would like us to remove your personal information, please contact us via our [Contact Us](http://www.participantmedia.com/contact) page and selecting “Request to remove information for a user believed to be under 13” from the Topic pulldown menu along with the details of your request.  Although we will try our best to remove the data you request, please note that the removal process does not ensure that everything will be completely deleted, especially once this content has been reposted or used on other websites.  Remember to think carefully before posting content on our website, as it can be difficult to remove completely.

We do not share any PII we collect from our users, including minors, for the third parties’ marketing purposes without first obtaining your consent or offering you an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing.

**_California / Delaware Do Not Track Disclosures_**

Various third parties are developing or have developed signals or other mechanisms for the expression of consumer choice regarding the collection of information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services (e.g., browser do not track signals).  Currently, we do not monitor or take any action with respect to these signals or other mechanisms.

_**International Users Outside the United States**_

The Service is operated in the United States, and all of the data is stored in the United States.  As a user of the Service, you agree to the information outlined in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, as well as the relevant United States laws that govern these documents.

By accessing or using our Service, or otherwise providing information to us, you give us permission to process or transfer any information that identifies you personally, as well as your aggregate data (summarized information) and details about your online habits, preferences, and experiences into the United States.

_**Security**_

We implement commercially reasonable physical and electronic security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of your personal information.  However, we cannot and do not guarantee that your personal information will never be breached or viewed by someone other than Company.

_**Changes to this Privacy Policy**_

From time-to-time, we may modify this Privacy Policy.  By continuing to use the Service after we post a revised Privacy Policy, you are accepting the terms outlined in the new Privacy Policy.  Therefore, it is important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated about any changes.

_**Contact Information**_

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via our [Contact Us](http://www.participantmedia.com/contact) page or at:

Participant Media, LLC  
ATTN: Privacy  
331 Foothill Road, 3rd Floor  
Beverly Hills, CA 90210
